Life as war
Naqoyqatsi is a documentary film directed by Godfrey Reggio.
A visual montage portrait of our contemporary world
dominated by globalized technology and violence.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Marlon Brando.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Elton John.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Julia Louis-Dreyfus.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Madonna.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Adolf Hitler.
Self (archive footage) (uncredited), played by Bill Clinton.
Naqoyqatsi is a 2002 American non-narrative film directed by Godfrey Reggio
and edited by Jon Kane, with music composed by Philip Glass.
It is the third and final installment in the Qatsi trilogy.
The title comes from the Hopi word naqö̀yqatsi meaning "life of war".
In the film's closing credits, the title is also translated as
"civilized violence" and "a life of killing each other".